(Penny:)I mean, not to the same people,
but...
There's gotta be someplace special
we could do it.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, where did you envision
marrying Penny?
(Leonard:)Will you shut up?
(Raj:)I know how to make it special.
(Howard:)I told you, we are not re-creating
the wedding from The Sound ofMusic.
(Raj:)Yes, you made that brutally
clear to me.
(Raj:)What I was going to suggest is...
...if you're willing
to wait until Sunday morning...
(Raj:)...the Google satellite
will be over Pasadena.
You can have your wedding
photographed from space.
- Whoa.
That's so cool.
- Way to go, Raj.
- I keep telling you.
(Raj:)If I wasn't an astrophysicist,
I would've been a party planner.
It was always a coin-flip.
(Howard:)Okay, so we know
we're gonna do it Sunday morning.
(Howard:)Now we need to find a good place
for the satellite to see us.
(Leonard:)How about our roof?
- Oh, I like that.
- That's great.
(Amy:)Oh, my gosh.